
Please contact me at chaoliner@gmail.com with any questions.

-----------------
 COMMAND CONSOLE
-----------------
This system allows a user to enter raw C# code into their game at runtime and have it executed.
To set up this system, drag the "Console Canvas" and "Console Open Listener" prefabs from the prefabs folder into your scene.
To use this system, simply press ~ to open the console, type some C# code into the input field at the bottom of the screen, and press enter. (Or Ctrl+Shift.)

OBJECT SELECTION:
Right-click an object to select it. You can now refrence so in your code as a variable. For example, you could type MonoBehaviour.Destroy(so);.
If you change the value of so, it will be availible in future commands. For example, if I type so = GameObject.Find("Cube");, and in my next command Debug.Log(so.Name);, Cube might show up in the Console.

AUTO-TYPE HOTKEYS:
In the hotkeys tab of the central bar, you will be able to find several buttons that automatically type useful code snippets for you. The buttons also list hotkeys that can be used to auto-type their snippets.
These code snippets include utilities for destroying, summoning, physics-pushing, and debug logging, along with others.
Note that some of these snippets involve pointing your mouse at a location, having an object selected and/or having an object with a rigidbody selected, and will throw an error otherwise.
If you want to create your own hotkeys, open CommandConsole in your code editor and add "hotkeys.Add(new Hotkey(KeyCode.<keycode>, "Name", "//code", 0));" near the beginning of the Start() function.

ENCLOSING CODE:
In oder to appease the compiler gods, your code is sandwiched between two other pieces of code.
In some circumstances, it may be necessary to look at or modify this code.
That's what the "Show/Edit enclosing code" button does.

COMMAND SCROLLING:
This feature allows you to revisit previous commands. Use Ctrl+↑ and Ctrl+↓ to scroll though commands, or the buttons on the central bar.

AUTOCOMPLETE:
When you first open the console, the autocomplete system will take a few seconds to populate its dictionary. It is ready when the dialog box at the top of the screen has closed.
When you have autocomplete enabled, the system will suggest ways to complete any word you are working on. Click a suggestion to use it. Green suggestions are from the UnityEngine and mscorlib assemblies.
Press Alt to use the bottommost suggestion.

BUTTONS:
You can use the Unity Editor to add buttons to the central bar of the console with no consequences.
If you want to remove a button, disable it instead of deleting it.